-Okay, Chandler.
-Okay.
And your horoscope says:
"On the 5th, a special
someone will give you a gift."
Well, thank you in advance.
"But the 12th brings a lover's spat."
You're going to make fun
of my present.
Why would you do that?
Wait. "On the 19th,
a secret crush announces itself."
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
It's Joey Tribbiani
of Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
That's right. It's your first day.
Are you psyched to fight crime
with your robot sidekick?
Am I?
The lead in my own TV series?
I've dreamed about this for years!
Why have I not been preparing?
You're gonna be great.
But I gotta act with a robot.
I know nothing about technology.
I can't even use Chandler's computer,
except to find porn.
And that's only because
it's there when you turn it on.
Our spat will start early this month.
I'll be waiting.
The One Where Ross Meets Elizabeth's Dad
Are you judging them by their covers?
You're really not supposed to.
I'm deciding which one to use. I'm
going to write another book.
Because the last one
was such a big seller?
If you must know,
I have written 14 books.
And as I'm the only one
who has read them...
I can tell you that
they have been well received.
But I lost all of them in the fire.
So this one I'm gonna keep in an
asbestos-lined box far away from Rachel.
Who I forgive.
What are you doing later?
Rachel and I have to get our hair cut.
-We do?
-I wanna see what he wants.
Elizabeth's dad wants to meet me.
Wait a minute. Hold the phone.
You're not Elizabeth's dad?
That's the only one you get.
And he hates me.
He asked Elizabeth why she'd want
to go out with a guy...
who couldn't get a girl his own age.
And what did she say to that?
And that's yours.
Come on. I really want
this guy to like me.
It would really help if you guys
could make me look good.
-Of course we'll help.
-Thanks.
We know how tough those
parent-teacher conferences can be.
-So here's your office set.
-Wow!
Mac Machiavelli, private investigator.
Look at all the books I've read.
Let's get you to wardrobe.
When do I meet the robot?
Right now. He's right here.
Joey Tribbiani, this is..
Wow! He's so lifelike.
Unbelievable.
This is Wayne, the man who created
and operates C.H.E.E.S.E.
How do you do there, buddy?
I'll let you two guys get acquainted.
Sorry about that.
-So where's C.H.E.E.S.E.?
-C.H.E.E.S.E. is right here.
Nice to meet you, Mac.
-This is the temporary robot, right?
-No. Why?
I thought it was gonna be
a really cool robot.
Like the Terminator,
or when I first saw you.
I spent two years developing this.
It's state of the art.
Sorry. It doesn't look like
it can do anything.
It can do this.
This is my father, Paul Stevens.
Dad, this is Ross Geller.
It's great to meet you, Paul.
I prefer that Liz's boyfriends
address me as Mr. Stevens.
Of course. Mr. Stevens.
So, Ross...
what's your problem?
Excuse me?
Why can't you get a girlfriend
your own age?
It's funny...
It's not funny.
I don't like you going out
with my daughter, Ross.
Okay, I can see that.
I think if you give me one chance,
I can change your mind.
-Okay.
-What?
Okay. I'll give you one chance
to change my mind.
You've got one minute.
-Daddy.
-Fine. Two minutes. Go.
A minute and 50 seconds.
I want you to know, I've
never done anything like this before.
I mean, I've been in relationships
in general.
But I've never done it with a student.
I mean, not...
Not "it." We haven't done "it."
I mean, we've done stuff...
Okay. A joke. Lighten the mood.
Two guys go into a bar.
One of them is Irish.
-I'm Irish.
-And the Irish guy wins the joke.
Ross! How crazy
that we would run into you.
Oh, my God! Thank you.
I'd like you to meet my friends.
This is Phoebe, Monica and Chandler.
-Phoebe.
-Hello.
-Monica.
-Hi.
Chunder.
-Chandler.
-Never going to remember that.
You're Elizabeth's dad?
I see where she gets her...
rugged handsomeness.
Is there a Mrs. Stevens?
There's a Mr. Bing!
Unfortunately, Lizzie's mom passed
away after she was born.
I raised her by myself.
I get that a lot.
Why don't we all take a seat?
I'll get us all some coffees.
Yeah, why don't you...
Talk about
whatever you want.
Whatever pops into your head.
It is strange seeing Ross here,
this time of day...
because usually
he's at the children's hospital.
But not looking for dates.
Monica is Ross's sister.
He's a great brother!
I had a sister.
She passed away.
You don't have to do that every time.
But Ross is a great guy.
I was roommates with him in college.
Funny story...
Your roommate in college died,
didn't he?
A part of him did, yes.
Here we are, Paul, Elizabeth.
I hope you guys are finding
something to talk about.
-Yes. We were just..
-Sorry I'm late.
But I am ready to talk you up.
-When does Liz's father get here?
-I'm already here.
Ross is so great!
Hey, Phoebe.
How's the book writing going?
Really well. I'm up to page 47.
-Wow! What are you writing?
-Page numbers.
Honey, you got the kind
with the little girl.
You said you'd buy the kind
with the baby.
-You said the baby creeps you out.
-The little girl does.
-You said the baby.
-Why would a baby creep me out?
Why would the little girl
creep you out?
Can you please talk a little slower?
-This is for your book?
-It's about relationships.
The traps, the pitfalls,
what not to do.
Keep going. This stuff's great.
Excuse me.
And how none of it matters when
the people really love each other.
And how people will believe anything
as long as it's a compliment.
-Oh, hi!
-Hi.
-I left my keys here somewhere.
-Well, let's look for them.
Hey, look! Are these them?
No.
All right.
-Here they are.
-Good.
-Thanks for your help.
-Wait! Sorry!
-Mr. Paul?
-Just call me Paul.
Paul.
I just wanted you to know that...
Ross really is a great guy.
Maybe you could date him. It'd
save me the trouble of killing him.
Are you okay?
You don't look old enough
to have a 20-year-old daughter.
Well, we were very young
when we had her.
-We?
-It usually takes two people to...
Oh, no! Yes! Of course. I know that!
What I meant was are you still "we"
or are you just you?
I'm just me.
My wife died shortly after
Lizzie was born.
So you raised her all on your own?
Yes, I did.
-What are you writing there?
-I'm drawing a picture of you.
Well, that's very flattering.
But it'd be great if you could draw me
with some clothes and a head.
How was your first day?
Pretty good. Except I got
attitude from the robot.
Damn those robots. They're supposed
to be our faithful servants!
It was the guy who controls the robot.
He hates me. He had C.H.E.E.S.E.
knock over the sandwich table...
right when I was reaching for one.
Why don't you get him fired?
I may have to. I hate to do it.
But I'm the star, you know?
There's a limit to how many sandwiches
I can eat off the floor.
Excuse me.
Joey Tribbiani.
Joe! I'm glad I found you!
I got an audition for you.
But it's kind of on the q.t.
The actor who has the part
doesn't know he might be fired.
It's the lead in a series.
Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
I'm the lead in Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
Joey?
Hi, Ross.
I was just getting him to like you.
Joey!
Ross, Joey is not here.
I'll just wait for him in here!
Ross, it's okay. You can come out.
Yeah. It's okay. It's me...
Mr. Stevens.
I didn't... Oh, my gosh.
I didn't even see you.
You did. You came in, got all awkward
and ran to the bedroom.
You were shouting, "Joey!"
-Bye, Rachel.
-Bye.
I'll call you later.
-See you.
-Bye, Ross.
What? What the..? How did...? What?
You know, he lost his keys.
So he was looking for them.
In your mouth?
No!
Downstairs. And we got to talking...
for two hours. I liked him.
I invited him for coffee.
You were at the coffeehouse!
What's the big deal?
So I kissed the guy.
He is my girlfriend's father.
It's weird!
-You dated my sister!
-That was different!
-What? Why?
-This is weird for me!
Ross, look. This is good for you.
Let's face it.
So far the guy's not loving you.
But I can turn that around.
I've got the inside track.
We could all go out to dinner.
And I could talk you up.
Plus the guy
is a very successful lawyer.
-How is that important?
-It's important!
There's a million guys
who can play Mac...
and there's one robot.
And this one guy who controls it.
I didn't know he could get me fired.
-What am I gonna do?
-You're a pretty charming guy.
Thanks. But I have a problem
to deal with.
No, you've got to win over
the guy who controls C.H.E.E.S.E.
Go back there
and kiss some serious robot ass!
That's not a bad idea!
If I have to be charming tomorrow,
I'm not wasting it on you guys.
I got some saved for you, Phoebe.
Do you think Joey is
more charming than me?
Yeah. That's why I'm sleeping
with him on the side.
You wish.
"You wish."
Stop writing about us.
I'm not writing about you.
I'm writing about other people.
-Who?
-Marsha and Chester.
Fine. Then you know what?
I will just write about Phyllis.
-"Phyllis is sitting in the chair."
-I see what you're doing.
"Phyllis sees what I'm doing."
I have tasted my own medicine
and it is bitter!
Morning!
How's my favorite genius
and his robot?
-Don't touch him!
-Okay.
Level with me. I keep hearing
rumors that I might get fired.
They even have actors reading
for my part.
Come on. You gotta give me
a second chance.
I love this little guy.
That's why you didn't want me
to touch him, right?
I can't believe it. God!
Hey, how are you doing?
So it seemed that my prom date
had stood me up.
So Ross selflessly offered to take me.
What a nice story.
So Ross was in college...
and decided to jump at the chance
to take a young girl to her prom.
I definitely did not see
that one backfiring.
-I'm going to the bathroom.
-Take your time.
I was a freshman and she was a senior.
So it wasn't as bad as..
Look. I know I've been giving you
a lot of jabs.
It's partly because
I'm very protective of Lizzie...
and partly because
they just keep coming to me.
I admit after all the
wonderful things Lizzie told me...
and the many, many, many stories
that Rachel has told me...
well...
you're not...
all bad.
"Not all bad."
I'm sorry I was so harsh.
But you have to understand.
I still look at Lizzie
like she's a 12-year-old girl.
I know what you mean. I do that too.
-I beg your pardon?
-I don't see her as a 12-year-old.
I mean, I have a son who is 6
and I still think of him as a baby.
-A son?
-My ex-wife and I share custody of Ben.
Incidentally, Carol and I
are on excellent terms...
as I'm sure you are with your wife.
I'm sorry.
It's unbelievable!
Don't worry. I didn't realize
you were married.
We were. But that was just a...
That was just a big drunken mistake.
You're back.
You two were married?
I'm sorry.
You were talking about Emily.
We said we would meet
at the coffeehouse at 6:00.
We said 7:00.
We said 6:00!
The only way that I said 6:00...
would be if I said the sentence,
"Let's meet at 7:00, not at 6:00."
If I had said 7:00, I would have said:
"My boyfriend is such a
wiseass. 7:00!"
-Hi!
-Oh, my good God!
-I know what time you said.
-What?
Well, I know what time
Chester and Marsha said.
What time?
Interesting turn of events.
Suddenly it's my book to the rescue.
Let's see.
Very interesting.
Well this certainly clears things up.
What does it say?
I will tell you as soon as you thank
me for writing my book.
Thank you for writing your book.
It's a great book...
and you are the
queen of everything.
Thanks. So are you.
I told you I should
not wear this color.
"Monica.. Marsha and Chester are
planning on seeing a movie Sunday.
"Marsha thinks they're meeting at
6:00. Chester thinks it's 7:00."
-You knew we were gonna miss the movie?
-Right.
Instead of telling us, you decided
to write it in your stupid book?
"Marsha and Chester
are mad at Phyllis."
I can't believe
I'm gonna lose this job.
I'm so sorry, man.
Is there anything I can do?
Help me get this mini-fridge
past the security guard.
Joey, I want to talk to you.
I don't want to talk to you.
I hate you. You ruined my life.
-Chandler, Wayne. Wayne, Chandler.
-Hi.
I'll get you your job back
if you help me out.
Why should I help you out?
-The reason he just said.
-What do you need?
I saw you on stage talking
to that beautiful woman.
You know, Sarah.
I wish I could talk to her.
-Are you in love with her?
-Yeah.
Her. All of them. Anyone.
Yeah. I've been there, my friend.
Listen, I guarantee you
keep your job...
if you can teach me to talk
to women like you do.
You can't teach it.
It's something you're born with.
You can teach it.
I can show you right now.
-Really?
-Sure. Yeah. I taught him.
Yeah. You should see the woman I'm with,
way out of my league.
In fact, if you want, I can get you her.
Well, if you think about it...
Ross did learn something
from each marriage.
How to make the next one even shorter?
Wait a minute. That's not fair.
He was married to me a hell of a lot
longer than he was to Emily.
He just didn't tell me.
Maybe I have to pee again.
Well, this is fun.
So, Ross, did you kill any
of these wives?
I have had enough of this! I
care a great deal about your daughter.
And I have treated her with respect!
So if you've got a problem with me..
-Are you yelling at me?
-God, no.
You know what?
If you don't like Ross, that's fine.
It doesn't matter.
I'm going out with him anyway.
Really?
Well, if it doesn't matter to her...
it doesn't matter to me.
Still not yelling.
What can I say?
I still don't like you.
I'm not so crazy
about myself right now either.
-Then we agree?
-I guess so.
-Neither of us like Ross.
-I like Ross.
Kids!
I just thought of a story
about how nice Ross is.
That's okay.
We're not liking Ross right now.
Well, I got a lot of those too.
You were right, C.H.E.E.S.E.
-The shipment never made it to Omaha?
-You got it.
And the rabbi's beard?
100 percent horsehair.
Nice catch, C.H.E.E.S.E.
It's your line, C.H.E.E.S.E.
Wayne! Wayne!